

DESMOND HAMILTON Web developer

O Brooklyn, NY

☑ DesHamilton25@outlook.com

% 347-445-6983

SOCIAL

in @dlh25

f @desmond.hamilton.9

@ @shadowham5

PROFILE

Security officer / Control room operator with more than 8 years of professional experience. Seeking a career change where I can leverage my proficiency skills in Figma, React, JavaScript, Node.js, MongoDB, CSS,and the MERN software stack, into a full-time career.

EDUCATION

Engineering CodingBootcamp

COLUMBIA UNIVERSITY 2018 - 2019

Advertisement Design

NEW YORK CITY COLLEGE OF TECHNOLOGY

2004 - 2008

SKILLS

- Html React.js
- P Css Figma
- JavaScript WordPress

EXPERIENCE

NYC Urban Professional League | Referee

From 2013 to Present

Communicate with players quickly and efficiently to make decisions. Demonstrate extensive knoledge of rules and policies. Officiate at sporting events, maintain standards safety of the players.

Allied Universal Security Service | Control Room Operator

From 2014 to Present

Collaborate with groups of twenty or more to run daily operations. Maintain real-time logs, compile reports, and make detailed record-keeping. Monitor all operations on screens, computers, radios, and paperwork.

Volo Sports | Referee

From 2016 to Present

Arrived early every workday to inspect the courts. Responsible for ensuring the safety of the players while educating on how to play the game.

CERTIFICATES

Columbia Engineering Coding Boot Camp (2019)

For attening and successfully completed the Executive Education program.

Udemy Certificate The Modern Javascript Bootcamp (2022)

Gain experience in the most up-to-date JS resource with two of Udemy's greatest instructors - Colt Steele and Stephen Grider

Udemy certificate by completing entire course (2023)

Master Mobile and Web Design, User Interface + User Experience (UI/UX Design), HTML, and CSS, Prototyping

REFERENCES

Nurse Practitioner

Mr. Alexander Trost

Phone: 917-921-4179

Email: Alexander.Trost@palliativistnyc.com

Supervisor

Mr. Angel Solano

Phone: 917-743-4929 Email: SolanoA@si.edu

LANGUAGES

English

INTERESTS

Music Travel Family Fitness